

EXPERIENCE

HR & Assistant of CEO (Contract) Shipnity Co., Ltd. JUL 2021 - Present

Chief of employee relation section (HR) Sri Trang Gloves Co., Ltd. AUG 2020 - JUN 2021

Teacher assistant and Tutor
Thammasat University
FEB 2019 - JUL 2019
TU108: Self Development and
Management class
TU113: Fundamentals of philosophy
class

EDUCATION

Thammasat University

Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy, Minor in Anthropology Second class Honours GPA 3.37 2016 - 2020

CONTACT

Mobile: 084-309-2903

E-mail: po.chanasorn@gmail.com Address: 48/259 Mayfair place

Sukhumvit 64 Bangchak Phra Khanong

Bangkok 10260

CHANASORN POTHIKRUPRASERT

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 16 FEB 1998

Interests/Hobbies: Movie, Music, Game, Philosophy, Sport

PROFILE

I am looking for a new opportunity to improve my acquired skills. I expect for the working environment that focuses on team building. I am an open-minded person who are always welcome for criticisms.

One year work experience grants me the essential basics of all work i.e. coordination , working with time period, adaptability. All these basics shall make me a comfortable choice that can easily fit in with your organization.

My responsibilities as HR were undertaking alien document applications such as VISA and Work Permit for Non-Thai employee, recruitment, performing Social Security Office's services for the employees such as registration and benefits, and etc.

My main responsibility as HR & Assistant is to facilitate team expanding process for new business unit and other delegated work form CEO.

SKILLS

- Self-management and Working independently
- Critical thinking and Creative thinking
- Microsoft office
- Conceptual analysis
- Collaboration
- Adaptive
- Reading for interpretation
- Participant Observation
- TOEIC 690